{
    "id": "7daae77b6ae3433887a989cd1b06bdd7",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The library has …………………………… of books.",
            "description": "Write lots or a lot.",
            "answers": [
                "lots",
                "lot"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4fe950d65d0342c2b5292a3fd9115a0c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………………… of the ship ended his career as a captain.",
            "description": "Loss is a noun. Lose is the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "loss",
                "lose",
                "loose"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "799be85a4d4d48e6ab821e78f9eebe19"
        },
        {
            "question": "The …………………………… file was never found.",
            "description": "Lost can be an adjective. ",
            "answers": [
                "lost",
                "loss",
                "losed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4bb6724283f5494789eff2fdba268a78"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog ran …………………………… in the yard.",
            "description": "Loose is the opposite of tight.",
            "answers": [
                "lose",
                "loose",
                "loss"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "deea3ebf29094206b5a8ac626ec61031"
        },
        {
            "question": "The plan was presented in a ………………………….. manner.",
            "description": "Logical is the adjective. Logic is a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "logic",
                "logical"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "192a2c013db1424fb902030fa16e0f13"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ……………………………. the prisoners’ bonds and set them free.",
            "description": "Loosed is the past tense of loose which can also be a verb. As a verb loose means untie.",
            "answers": [
                "loosed",
                "losed",
                "lost"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "45504b5444bd4e62a12c6627670db309"
        },
        {
            "question": "The play’s ………………………….. is Mumbai.",
            "description": "Locale means setting.",
            "answers": [
                "local",
                "locale"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5f105c30e3864ac19cd26071328ec0ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "The salesman is …………………………. to accept a job in a new territory.",
            "description": "Loath means unwilling or averse.",
            "answers": [
                "loath",
                "loathe"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cd4a0dde2a3c4206af841006445ad6e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "They …………………………. pretension.",
            "description": "Loathe means hate.",
            "answers": [
                "loath",
                "loathe"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2a95358421414d74b4703110894ba356"
        },
        {
            "question": "A few luxuries make life more …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "livable",
                "liveable",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f227dbe1773544109b92464bdaf98bb5"
        },
        {
            "question": "If we make a ………………………… effort we will win the game.",
            "description": "Collective means unified.",
            "answers": [
                "collective",
                "collected"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "42bffaef869046f4a908ed32566c53b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The witness was remarkably ……………………………… under the cross examination.",
            "description": "Collected means self controlled.",
            "answers": [
                "collective",
                "collected"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "98a3ba44b94e4785a881a18c99547856"
        }
    ]
}